<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="webtek\style.css"?>	

<faq>
	<title>Sad Penguin Fun Shop</title>
	<subtitle>FAQ</subtitle>
	<question>Why is the sky blue?</question>
	<answer>Someone had some left over paint. You know it was not always blue it use to be grey. I know this because when
	I was watching an really old film made like a million years ago or something the sky in that film was grey. However it is also
	rumoured that the sky is blue from holding its breath.</answer>
	<question>Can cows laugh?</question>
	<answer>No, cows can indeed not laugh. If they could milk would come out their nose.</answer>
	<question>What is the largest sheet that I can scan?</question>
	<answer>8.5 × 14 inches (216 × 356 mm).</answer>
	<question>Is there life after death?</question>
	<answer>Death is not the ending of life, only of the fragment we call the self. Nor is death the opposite of life; it is part of life, 
	as natural and essential as birth. The self is grounded in the past. That is, the entity we call ‘me’ is made up of memories, knowledge, 
	beliefs, ideas, which are based on past impressions, past experience. These give us a sense of continuity, but life is not continuous. 
	Each moment of ‘now’ is entirely new: it has never been, nor will be again. We meet life with what we know, with the past, and so are 
	rarely fully awake to the ‘now’. Death is the ending of all we know, and many of us are afraid of it. We want the familiar to continue; we would like to enjoy another summer, to meet a loved-one one more time. But what we fear and desire are projections of our imagination, and hence are also based on the past. Not knowing death, what we truly fear is the idea of death. Each moment that we spend fearing or desiring what might be is a moment we are not fully awake to life.
	To live fully in the present the self must end, which means ending all attachment to what has been. 
	Then you are not separate from life, which has no beginning and no end.</answer>
	<question>Will there be any questions about the web site, products or anything vaguely 
	connected to the awe inspiring web shop known as Sad Penguin Fun Shop? </question>
	<answer>Probably not.</answer>
	<question>Isn't that the point of a FAQ page? so you can easily give customers answers to frequently asked questions about
	your company?</question>
	<answer>Here at Sad Penguin Fun Shop we believe that all our customers deserve our full attention. We will therefore personally 
	answer all questions personally through our contact page.   </answer>

	<question>Can I use the Virtual Reality Eye Drops with the 2D Glasses?</question>
	<answer>I believe this is a question that will be best answered if you contact us through the contact page.</answer>
	<question>Is Rick Deckard a replicant?</question>
	<answer> No, he is played by human actor Harrison Ford.</answer>

</faq>


